You're never Gonna get my love
Now because you where
Are the bros coming up ahead?
Oh,
sorry for the question,
are you from Jundiaí,
there's no way to keep this style from you,
otherwise it's not better.
go see there.
hello safe,
Leave the marketing guy here yet,
beauty?
it's fine.
good weekend to you.
you
stay with God.
bye bye.
i know you broke their watch
What happened The other night,
bit by bit.
good weekend there,
tamo together.
two real water
I sold four truffles to
of our trade,
bro,
everything is relationship,
It's on vei.
congratulations brother,
God bless.
tamo together.
oh,
at the party you don't call me,
you're too much Cara,
what a delight,
too much partner is.
por,
noticing something here to talk about,
being interesting and uninteresting is that bro,
sell OR not sell does not matter,
say hello and then it's fine,
thank god
I'm going there on the other side,
but I came just to say hello my brother.
I came by to say hi to you.
good weekend there,
all good?
I no longer unroll in the pamphlet today.
okay, okay,
you're a partner.
Oh,
you're going to be stylish,
man,
we see the type of closing a value with us,
for us to stop being curious.
pô serião
even though no barbershop gives a cocoa bonfire.
Show from
hand hour,
come on,
let's go
leave then.
I made the replacement,
John has already fallen and dented,
Wow, it's hot,
damn it.
I went to the gas station on foot,
then the guys fall,
where's your car?
I said,
there's the car bro?
and then I forgot that I came by car,
bro.
then I walked back,
now I'm going back to the post.
did you find the car?
I found the car.
if we are selling our time and effort
to earn less,
why not sell our time and effort to earn more?
i got to start being more strategic than that
and take a level to make more money,
man,
and I think I had an idea.
And is Say Now,
ready,
Set, GO
Do he think he made It Winner.